1984年6月28日
将军同志
Comrade-General.
我们接近了
We are close.
您能看到
You can see.
您能看到我们的进展
You can see our progress.
我们只是需要更多时...
We just need more ti--
给你一年时间
You have one year.
是  将军同志
Yes, Comrade-General.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     草草
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     大葱
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
怪奇物语 第三季 第一集
第一章
苏茜  收到吗
一年后
*现在没人想了解你了*
*And nobody wants to know you now*
-*没人想让你看到...*  -迈克
- *Nobody wants to show you-- *- Mike!
迈克  别闹了
Mike, stop! Stop!
-*如果你迷失而孤独*  -迈克  别唱了
- *So if you're lost and on your own* - Mike! Stop!
迈克
Mike! Mike!
-*千万不要放弃*  -别唱了
- *You can never surrender* - Stop!
-你不喜欢吗  -不
- What, you don't like it? - No!
别看狗  开你的锁
Don't look at the dogs, work the lock.
开锁  开锁  别看狗
Work the lock. Work the lock. Don't look at the dogs.
你看狗了
You looked at the dogs.
有时  一切都进行顺利
Sometimes everything goes exactly as planned.
至少留三英寸
Three-inch minimum!
门至少留三英寸
Leave the door open three inches!
一一  开门
El, open this door.
开门
Open the--
怎么了
What's wrong?
天呐  简直太逗了
My God, that was priceless!
你看到他的表情了吗
Did you see his face?
红得像番茄
It was like a tomato!
是啊  胖番茄
Yeah, a fat tomato.
-真希望你还在这里  -我知道
- I wish I was still with you. - I know.
我也希望
Me too.
但我们明天一早就见
But I'll see you tomorrow, all right? First thing.
那就明天
Tomorrow.
星庭商场
-你迟到了  -抱歉
- You're late. - Sorry!
-又迟了  -我们要错过开幕了
- Again. - We're gonna miss the opening.
如果你们还继续抱怨的话  快走
Yeah, if you keeping whining about it. Let's go!
"如果你们还继续抱怨的话"
"If you guys keep whining about it."
-别说话了  哥们  -我猜猜
- Just please stop talking, dude. - Let me guess.
你忙去了
You were busy.
是啊  真成熟  卢卡斯
Oh, yeah, real mature, Lucas.
"一一  真希望我们能一直亲热
"Oh, El, I wish we could make out forever,
再不跟朋友们玩了"
and never hang out with any of our friends."
卢卡斯  别闹了
Lucas, stop.
-威尔觉得好笑  -的确好笑
- Will thinks it's funny. - Because it is.
是啊  真好笑
Yeah, it's so funny that
我居然想跟女友度过浪漫时光
I want to spend romantic time with my girlfriend.
我也在跟我女友度过浪漫时光呢
I'm spending romantic time with my girlfriend.
借过  抱歉
Excuse us! Sorry! Sorry!
抱歉
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
-借过  抱歉  -抱歉
- Excuse me, I'm sorry. - Sorry.
小心点
Watch it!
是啊  小心点  书呆子
Yeah! Watch it, nerd!
你不是该睡觉了吗
Isn't it past your bedtime?
你不是该去死了吗
Isn't it time you died?
-疯子  -蠢蛋
- Psycho! - Butthead!
-购物狂  -屁脸
- Mall rat! - Fart face!
你可真成熟呢
Oh, now that was mature.
海员勺  冰淇淋店
呆瓜  你的孩子来了
Hey, dingus, your children are here.
又来  不是吧
Again? Seriously?
快点
Come on, come on.
我发誓  如果有人知道了
I swear, if anybody hears about this--
我们死定了
We're dead!
安全
All clear.
丧尸出笼
看  卢卡斯  我们进来了
See, Lucas? We made it.
-我们错过了预告片  -还是赶上了  屁脸
- We missed the previews. - Still made it. Fart face.
-彩虹糖  -谢谢
- Skittles. - Thanks.
-拜托  -拜托
- Come on! - Come on!
搞什么
The hell?
好奇怪
That's weird.
那样没用  呆瓜
That isn't gonna work, dingus.
真的吗
Oh, really?
要有光
Let there be light.
你没事吧
You okay?
嗯
Yeah.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
当然
Of course.
没事
Okay.
该死
Shit!
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit!
-怎么了  -快9点了
- Wh-- What's wrong? - It's almost 9:00.
-什么  -我们忘记重设闹铃了
- What? - We forgot to reset the clocks.
-昨晚停电了  不是吗  -该死
- The power went out last night, remember? - Oh, shit!
-等等  -不  我上班再吃
- Wait up. - Oh, no, I'll eat at work.
-我迟到了  -不
- I'm late. - No.
-你的脸  -好了
- Your cheek. - All right, all right.
-我得走了  回见  -好吧
- I gotta run. See you later. - All right.
恶心
Gross.
我看等你恋爱了
Well, I don't think you're gonna think
就不会觉得恶心了
it's gross when you fall in love.
我不会恋爱的
I'm not gonna fall in love.
好吧
Okay.
这是怎么了
What happened here?
我不知道
I don't know.
鲍勃·纽比  超级英雄
你能再开快点吗
Can you please drive faster?
你希望车坏掉吗
Do you wanna break down?
这玩意还能开就算我们走运了
We're lucky this thing still drives at all.
真的  乔纳森  我不能迟到
I'm serious, Jonathan, I can't be late.
是我们不能迟到
You mean we can't be late.
不  是我不能迟到
No, I mean I can't be late.
不管你做什么他们都喜欢你
They like you no matter what you do.
他们也喜欢你
Hey, they like you too.
是啊  他们喜欢我这个端咖啡机器
Yeah. They like that I'm a coffee delivery machine.
他们并不喜欢  或尊重我
They don't actually like me or respect me
是个活生生能呼吸有脑子的人类
as a living, breathing human with a brain.
等等  你只需要耐心点  好吗
Wait, you just-- you just gotta be patient, okay?
他们比较传统
They're set in their ways, you know?
但等他们意识到你是多有天赋的写手
But... once they realize what a gifted writer you are,
他们就会回心转意
they'll come around.
我现在真不需要乔纳森·拜耶斯的鼓励
I really don't need a Jonathan Byers pep talk right now.
你能不能  再开快点
Can you just... please drive faster?
好吧
Okay.
这里是金领袖  正在返回基地  收到吗  完毕
This is Gold Leader, returning to base. Do you copy? Over.
我重复  这里是金领袖
I repeart. This is Gold Leader,
正在返回基地  收到吗  完毕
returning to base. Do you copy? Over.
-我重复  这里是该死的金领袖  -达斯汀
- I repeart. This is goddamn Gold Leader-- - Dusty!
-怎么了  -放松  老天爷啊
- What? - Relax! For goodness' sake.
我在范围内  他们该回复的
I'm in range. They should be answering.
你走了一个月  亲爱的  或许他们...
You've been away a whole month, honeybun. Maybe they just...
忘了
forgot.
至少还有人欢迎我回来
At least someone's happy I'm home.
我是在做梦
It's just a dream.
你在做梦
You're dreaming.
停
Now!
欢迎回家  达斯汀
深水炸弹
Cannonball!
马可
Marco!
波罗
Polo!
马可
Marco!
波罗
Polo!
马可
Marco!
波罗
Polo!
马可
Marco!
波罗
Polo!
马可
Marco!
波罗
Polo!
女士们
Ladies.
她下来了
She's coming down.
好戏开场
And... showtime.
胖墩
Hey, lard-ass!
有我在不许跑
No running on my watch!
要我再说一次  我就终身禁止你来
I gotta warn you again, and you're banned for life.
你想被终身禁止吗  胖墩
You wanna be banned for life, lard-ass?
我猜也是
Didn't think so.
下午好  女士们
Afternoon, ladies.
下午好  比利
Afternoon, Billy.
新泳装真好看  维勒太太
Dig the new suit, Mrs. Wheeler.
谢谢
Thank you.
出租
拯救镇中心  别去商场  镇政厅星期二晚6点  拒绝星庭
梅维达综合商店
打折
你忙吗
You busy?
你是我们第一位客人  所以
You're our first customer, so...
又怎么了
What now?
然后一一  她就把门摔上了
And then El, she just... slams the door.
就当我面摔上了
Right in my face.
就怪那个自大的臭小子  迈克
You know, it is that smug son of a bitch, Mike.
他把她都带坏了  相信我
He's corrupting her, I'm telling you.
我要失控了  真的  乔伊
And I'm just gonna lose it. I mean, I am gonna lose it, Joyce.
放松点  霍普
Just take it down, Hopper.
我需要他们分手
I need for them to break up.
那不是你能决定的
That is not your decision.
他们在一起的时间绝对太多了
They're spending entirely too much time together.
你也赞同吧
You agree with me about that, right?
他们只是在接吻  是吧
Well, I mean, they're just kissing, right?
是啊  但简直一刻不停
Yeah, but it is constant.
一刻不停
It is constant.
好吗  这可不正常
Okay? That is not normal,
这不健康
that is not healthy.
你是不能逼他们分开的
You can't just force them apart.
他们不是小孩子了  霍普
I mean, they're not little kids anymore, Hop.
他们十几岁了
They're teenagers.
如果你像个警察似的命令他们
If you order them around like a cop,
他们会叛逆的
then they're gonna rebel.
孩子就这样
It's just what they do.
那怎么  我就对他们听之任之吗
So what, I'm just supposed to let them do whatever they want?
不  我没那么说  我觉得你该
No, I didn't say that. I think you should...
跟他们谈谈
talk to them.
不  不  谈话没用的
No. No. 'Cause talking doesn't work.
不是吼  不是命令
Not yelling. Not ordering.
是谈话
But talk to them.
交心地谈谈
You know, like a heart-to-heart.
交心
A heart-to-heart?
那是什么
What is that?
你叫他们坐下  跟他们谈谈  像朋友那样
You sit them down and you talk to them, like you're their friend.
我发觉  如果你跟他们平等地谈
I find if you talk to them like you're on their level,
他们就会听进去
then they really start to listen.
然后  你可以确立些规矩
And then, you know, you could start to create some boundaries.
-规矩  -是啊
- Boundaries. - Yeah, but,
但霍普  重要的是  不管他们如何反应
Hop, it's really important that no matter how they respond,
你都要保持冷静
you stay calm.
你绝不能发火
You cannot lose your temper.
或许你可以替我去
Maybe you could do it for me?
不行
No.
你可以的  你下班后过来
Yeah, you could. Yeah, you could. You come over after work.
-行的  -不行
- Yes. - No.
只有你说才行
It only works if it comes from you.
但是
But...
-但是  -我或许能帮你
- But? - Maybe I can help you...
调整措辞
find the right words.
霍金斯邮报
-谢谢  亲爱的  -给你的
- Thanks, hon. - For you.
给你的
For you.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thanks. - Welcome.
不不  南茜
Oh, no, no, no, no! Nancy!
抱歉
Sorry.
-写篇伊朗的报道吧  -我想要本地新闻
- How 'bout a piece on Iran? - I want something local.
听说今年的嘉年华有选美
I hear there's a beauty pageant at the fair this year.
是啊  我想要上半版版面的内容  布鲁斯
Yeah, I'm looking for above the fold here, Bruce.
那你肯定是没见过露西·勒布洛克
Then clearly you haven't seen Lucy Lebrock,
上半版版面恐怕装不下她
because I'm not sure she'll fit above the fold!
各位
Fellas!
六小时后我们就付印了  我需要真新闻
In six hours, we go to print. I need something real.
那对儿应该是真的
Oh, I think they're real.
星庭怎么样
What about Starcourt?
我就是...
I-- I was just...
在想
thinking...
我知道大家都喜欢商场  但是
I mean, I know everyone loves the mall, but...
它开业后  有多少小店倒闭
how many small businesses have closed since it opened?
主街上就至少五家
Like, five on Main, at least.
这改变了我们小镇的结构
It's changing the fabric of our town
-可以说  -《美国小镇之死》
- in a way-- - "The Death of Small-Town America."
我喜欢
I like it.
我很喜欢
I like it a lot.
但我觉得我有更热辣的话题
But I think I've got something even spicier.
是我的汉堡包缺少的芥末酱
It's about the missing mustard on my hamburger.
你觉得你可以追查线索
You think you can follow the clues
解决失踪调味品迷案吗  神探南茜[少女侦探]
and solve the case of the missing condiment, Nancy Drew?
抱歉
Sorry.
小心  菲尔  她可能想要你的工作
Look out, Phil, she might be after your job!
好点了吗
Better?
还疼
Still stings.
你新长痘了吗
Is that a new zit?
你什么毛病
What is wrong with you?
我就是问问
I was just asking!
我称之为  永动钟
I call it... the Forever Clock.
好吗  风力推动  天启时肯定用得上
All right? Powered by wind. Very useful in the apocalypse.
然后是
Then, I give you...
大锤机
the Slammer.
不错吧
Pretty neat, huh?
但这个
But this...
这是我的杰作
this is my masterpiece.
见过
I would like you to meet...
脑波机
Cerebro.
这是什么啊
What exactly are we looking at here?
独一无二的未装配的电池驱动无线电塔
An unassembled one-of-a-kind battery-powered radio tower.
所以是  业余无线电
So, it's a... A ham radio.
是业余无线电里的凯迪拉克
The Cadillac of ham radios.
这玩意能在远距离内
This baby carries a crystal-clear connection
保持清晰信号
over vast distances.
跨南北极那种
I'm talking North Pole to South.
我可以随时随地跟我女友通话
I can talk to my girlfriend whenever and wherever I choose.
女友
Girlfriend?
等等  她叫苏茜吗
Wait, so her name is Suzie?
苏茜  茜的茜  犹他州的
Suzie with a "Z." She's from Utah.
还有女生去科学营
Girls go to science camp?
-苏茜就去  她是天才  -她好看吗
- Suzie does. She's a genius. - Is she cute?
想想菲比·凯茨  但她更性感
Think Phoebe Cates, only hotter.
-怎么回事  -去跟达斯汀的女友通话
- What's going on? - Going to talk to Dustin's girlfriend.
女友
Girlfriend?
好了  一勺巧克力  1.25块
Alrighty, one scoop of chocolate. That's a buck-twenty-five.
还需要别的吗
Anything else?
普渡大学
Ooh, Purdue.
-厉害  -嗯  我很期待
- Fancy. - Yeah, I'm excited.
是啊  我也考虑过
Yeah, you know, I considered it,
普渡大学  但我又想
Purdue, but then I was like, you know what?
我还是需要点生活历练
I really think I need some real-life experience, you know,
然后再去大学  体验下生活
before I hit college, see what it feels like.
就是
Kinda like, uh, I don't know,
体验下工作赚钱的生活  知道吗
see what it's like to earn a working-man's wage, you know?
抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
-我觉得那很重要  -当然了
- I think that's, like, really important. - Yeah, totally.
是啊  这很好玩的
Yeah, anyway, this was, like, so fun.
我们应该
We should kind of like, you know, I don't know,
或许这周一起出去玩什么的
maybe hang out this weekend or--
抱歉了
Oh, sorry about that.
或许  下周吧
I don't know. Maybe next weekend or--
我忙的
Yeah, I'm busy.
没事
Oh, that's cool. I'm--
我下周末还要在这里打工
I'm working here next weekend, so...
下下周末更好
the following weekend's better for me.
不  抱歉  我不能
No. I'm sorry, I can't.
好了  谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
我...
I...
我今天第一天在这里干
This is... my first day here.
又一个没上钩
And another one bites the dust.
你零比六了  大力水手
You are oh-for-six, Popeye.
你厉害  你真臭
我会数数
Yeah, yeah, I can count.
这表示你真臭
You know that means you suck.
是啊  我也识字
Yep, I can read, too.
谁说的
Since when?
就怪这顶破帽子
It's this stupid hat.
相信我  绝对影响了我的颜值
I am telling you, it is totally blowing my best feature.
是啊  公司政策最讨厌了
Yeah, company policy is a real drag.
这是个疯狂的想法  但你考虑过
You know, it's a crazy idea, but have you considered...
说实话吗
telling the truth?
你是说  我连理工都考不上
Oh, you mean, that I couldn't even get into Tech
我的混蛋老爸想给我个教训
and my douchebag dad's trying to teach me a lesson,
我时薪3美元  完全没有未来吗  这个实话
I make three bucks an hour, and I have no future? That truth?
12点钟
Hey, twelve o'clock.
该死  该死  好吧
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Okay...
我去了  好吗
I'm going in. Okay?
知道吗
And you know what?
去他的公司政策
Screw company policy.
天呐  你焕然一新了
Oh, my God, you're a whole new man.
是吧
Right?
两位女士好啊  没看到你们
Ahoy, ladies! Didn't see you there.
你们想跟我一起在美味之海上航行吗
Would you guys like to set sail on this ocean of flavor with me?
我来做你们的船长
I'll be your captain.
我是史蒂夫·哈灵顿
I'm Steve Harrington.
天呐
Oh, God.
你们想尝尝樱桃盛典吗
Can I get you guys a little taste of the Cherries Jubilee?
不吗  有人想来点吗
No? Anybody?
香蕉船  四个人  四个勺
Banana Boat? Four people, four spoons?
在包厢里一起吃  有人想吗  外面很热的
Share it in the booth? Anybody? It's hot out there.
你真臭
我知道谈这个很困难
I know this is a difficult conversation to have...
但我希望你知道  我非常在乎你
but I hope you know that I... care about you very much.
-我知道你...  -眼神接触
- And I know that you-- - Eye contact.
我知道
And I know that you...
你们都很在乎彼此
both care about each other very much.
这完全不像我说的话
This does not sound like me at all.
继续  加油
Just keep going. Come on.
所以我觉得
Which is why I think
我们一定要立下这些规矩
it's important to establish these boundaries...
以便今后...
moving forward...
别看  你行的
No looking. You know this.
加油
Come on.
...建立一个良好环境
...so we can build an environment...
让我们
where we...
都能感到自在
all feel comfortable
被信任
and trusted
开放
and open...
"分享我们的情绪"
"Share our feelings..."
可以分享我们的情绪  这不行
...to sharing our feelings-- This isn't gonna work.
不行  不行的
It's not gonna work. It's not gonna work.
能行的  我保证
Yes, it will! I promise.
拜托
Oh, come on.
要不我杀了迈克好了
Maybe I'll just kill Mike.
我是警察局长  我能掩盖起来
I'm the chief of police, I could cover it up.
你可以的
You got this.
我保证
I promise.
你今晚想一起吃饭吗
You wanna have dinner tonight?
你可以再指点指点我
You can give me some more pointers.
我...
Oh, I...
我
I...
我有安排了
I have plans.
好吧
Okay, sure.
来顾客了
A customer.
-卡洛  -乔伊
- Hey, Carol! - Oh, hi, Joyce!
你好吗  见到你太好了
How are you? So good to see you.
乔治的13岁生日要到了
So, um, Georgie has his 13th birthday coming up.
天呐  13了吗
Oh, my gosh, 13?
是啊
I know!
我有点不知所措...
And I'm a little lost...
我们还不够高吗
Aren't we high enough?
脑波机在一百米处运转最好
Cerebro works best at a hundred meters.
我确定犹他州的人也有电话的
You know, I'm pretty sure people in Utah have telephones.
是啊  但苏茜是摩门教徒
Yeah, but Suzie's Mormon.
该死  她没有电力吗
Oh, shit. She doesn't have electricity?
那是阿米什人
Oh, that's the Amish.
-那摩门教徒是什么  -非常虔诚的白人
- What are Mormons? - Super religious white people.
他们有电  有车  但是
They have electricity and cars and stuff, but...
因为我不是摩门教徒
since I'm not Mormon,
她父母绝不会允许我们交往
her parents would never approve.
挺
It's all a bit...
莎士比亚的
Shakespearean.
莎士比亚
Shakespearean?
是啊  就像罗密欧与朱丽叶
Yeah. Like Romeo and Juliet.
好吧
Right.
-被诅咒的恋人  -懂
- Star-crossed lovers. - I got it.
各位
Hey, guys!
这挺好玩的  但是
This is fun and all, but, uh...
我得回家了
I have to go home.
-我们快到了  -抱歉
- We're almost there. - Sorry, man.
宵禁
Curfew.
-走吧  -祝你们好运
- Come on, let's go. - Good luck.
-4点宵禁  -他们撒谎
- Curfew at 4:00? - They're lying.
-他们一夏天都这样  -挺浪漫的
- It's been like this all summer. - It's romantic.
-恶心  -扯淡
- It's gross. - It's bullshit.
我刚回家
I just got home.
反正是他们的损失
Well, their loss, right?
向上前进
Onwards and upwards!
苏茜还等着呢
Suzie awaits!
威尔  来啊
Will, come on!
游得不错啊  维勒太太
Looking good out there, Mrs. Wheeler.
谢谢
Thank you.
身型完美
Perfect form.
要说起来
Well...
你的身型才棒呢
your form is amazing.
抱歉  我是说
I'm sorry, I mean, I...
我见过你  教别人
I've seen you... uh, teaching...
教课  教游泳
...lessons. Swimming lessons.
我可以...
You know, I could, uh...
如果需要  我可以教你
I could teach you, if you like.
我知道各种姿势
I know all the styles.
自由泳
Freestyle.
蝶泳
Butterfly.
蛙泳[摸胸]
Breaststroke.
你没事吧
You okay?
我不知道你还教大人
I didn't think you... I didn't think you taught adults.
我向一部分
Well, I offer more,
精挑细选的客户提供高级课程
advanced lessons to select clientele.
想起来  康沃利斯街的
Come to think of it, there is a good pool
6号汽车旅馆的泳池很不错
out at a Motel 6 on Cornwallis.
没什么人
It's very quiet.
非常隐蔽
You know, very private.
今晚吧
Shall we say tonight?
8点
Eight o'clock?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不能
I can't.
不能什么  玩玩吗
Can't what? Have fun?
-维勒太太  -不行
- Mrs. Wheeler! - No.
我...觉得我不需要上课
I... I... I just, uh... I don't think I need any lessons.
可是  我觉得你需要
Oh, you see, I think you do.
我觉得你是老师没找对
I just don't think that you've had the right teacher.
-我...  -肯定会
- I, uh... - It will be
是你这辈子最棒的锻炼
the workout of your life.
到了
Made it.
是啊  只走了五小时
Yeah, only took five hours.
我们为什么不玩《龙与地下城》
Why couldn't we just play D&D?
我渴死了
I'm so thirsty.
你真把我们的水都喝光了吗
Did you seriously just drink the rest of our water?
挺厉害的吧
Pretty impressive, right?
-是啊  -准备认识我的爱人了吗
- Yeah. - Now, you ready to meet my love?
-好啊  -好
- Okay, sure. - Yeah.
苏茜  这里是达斯汀  你收到吗  完毕
Suzie, this is Dustin. Do you copy? Over.
稍等等  她可能...她还在的
One sec. She's probably... She's still there.
苏茜
Suzie...
这里是达斯汀  你收到吗  完毕
this is Dustin. Do you copy? Over.
她肯定在的  就是...
I'm sure she's there. It's just--
-嗯  -或许她在忙  什么的
- Yeah. - You know, maybe she's, like, busy or--
-是啊  -快吃晚饭了
- Yeah. - It's around dinnertime.
是啊
Yep.
这里是
Here.
苏茜  这里是达斯汀  你收到吗  完毕
Suzie, do you copy? This is Dustin. Over.
伙计们  我回来了
Hey, guys, I'm home.
伙计们
Guys?
有人吗
Hello?
你接下来想跟谁说话
So, who do you wanna speak to next?
我是说弗雷泽  萨姆
I'm talking about Frasier, Sam.
他今晚喝了几口红酒
He had a couple of sips of Chianti tonight
就向我求婚了
and asked me to marry him.
你是说喝了几桶吗
Did you say a couple of sips, or barrels?
-他们真逗  是吧  -是啊
- Ah, they're funny, don't you think? - Yes.
我希望他们赶快复合
I just wish they'd get back together again already.
我也希望
Me too.
你不是觉得我还...
You don't think that I still--
-当然了  -必须的
- Well, of course I-- - You bet your--
告诉大家  明天婚礼后我会打来
Tell everyone that I'll call after the wedding tomorrow.
明天  急什么
Tomorrow? What's the rush?
弗雷泽周到浪漫地
Frasier has thoughtfully and romantically
安排我们在马里奥庄园
arranged for us to be married
结婚了
at the Marino estate.
鲍比·纽比  超级英雄
该死
Shit, shit.
《霍金斯邮报》
Hawkins Post.
稍等
Hold on, I'm--
抱歉  你可以重复一遍吗
I'm sorry, can you-- can you repeat that?
朵丽丝·德里斯科尔  康沃利斯路4819号  疾病  老鼠
...所以一定要立下这些规矩
...why it's important to establish these boundaries...
以便今后建立一个良好环境
moving forward, so that we can create an environment where...
让你能感到自在  被信任  开放
you feel comfortable and trusted and open.
该死
Shit.
"可以分享我们的情绪"
"To share our feelings."
什么事
Yes?
可以跟你们谈谈吗
Can I talk to you guys a minute?
我...
What I, uh...
需要对你们说
needed to say to you...
我想
What I wanted
对你们说的
to say to you...
是...
is that, um...
我觉得我们有麻烦了
I think we're in trouble.
不是
No.
你们没惹麻烦  好吗
No, nobody's in trouble, okay?
我就是
I just, um...
知道吗
You know what?
你妈妈打来了
Your mom called.
什么
What?
是啊
Yeah.
她要你马上回家
She needs you home right away.
没出什么事吧
Is everything okay?
好像有事
No, I don't think so.
是你奶奶
It's your grandma.
-她死了吗  -没有
- Is she dead? - No.
-她又摔倒了吗  -不是
- Did she fall again? - No.
她得癌症了吗
Does she have cancer?
-不是  -那我不懂
- No. - Then I don't understand.
奶奶怎么了
What's wrong with Nana?
没事  奶奶没事
Nothing! There's nothing wrong with Nana!
-什么  -但是
- What? - But...
你跟一一的事  很不对
there's something very wrong with this thing between you and El.
你个撒谎的混蛋
Oh, you lying piece of shit!
你疯了
You're crazy!
疯了
Crazy?
你想见识真疯吗
You want to see real crazy?
你再敢不尊重我
You disrespect me again.
好吗
Okay?
接下来这样
Here's what's gonna happen.
我开车送你回家
I'm gonna drive you home.
我要说话
And I'm gonna speak...
你要听好
and you're going to listen.
然后或许
And then, maybe...
或许等我说完了  如果你走运  或许
maybe by the end of it, maybe if you're lucky, maybe...
我会继续
I will continue
允许你跟我女儿约会
to allow you to date my daughter.
听懂就点头
Nod if you understand!
收到吗  这里是达斯汀  完毕
...do you copy? This is Dustin. Over.
苏茜  这里是达斯汀  你收到吗  完毕
Suzie! This is Dustin. Do you copy? Over.
苏茜  这里是你的达斯汀  你收到吗  完毕
Suzie, this is your Dustin. Do you copy? Over.
-苏茜  -达斯汀  拜托  她不在
- Suzie-- - Dustin, come on! She's not there.
她在的  好吗  她会接的
She's there, all right? She'll pick up.
-或许脑波机不好使  -或许苏茜不存在
- Maybe Cerebro doesn't work. - Or maybe Suzie doesn't exist.
她存在
She exists!
她是天才  还比菲比·凯茨性感
She's a genius and she's hotter than Phoebe Cates?
没有姑娘那么完美
No girl is that perfect.
是吗
Is that so?
我是说...
I mean...
你就是完美的
you're perfect.
以你自己的方式完美
I mean, like, per-- perfect in your own way.
特别的...以你特别的方式完美
In your special-- your own special way.
放松  我逗你的
Relax, I was teasing.
我当然完美  达斯汀肯定在撒谎
I'm obviously perfect and Dustin's obviously lying.
走吧  唐璜
Come on, Don Juan.
-你们去哪  -回家
- Where are you going? - Home.
看来只剩你和我了  拜耶斯
Well... guess it's just you and me, Byers.
现在很晚了
It's late.
抱歉
Sorry.
或许我们明天玩《龙与地下城》吧
Maybe tomorrow we can play D&D.
或是玩点什么好玩的  就像以前那样
Or something fun. Like we used to?
好啊
Yeah, sure.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
嗯
Yeah.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
该死
Shit.
苏茜  苏茜  是你吗
Suzie? Suzie, is that you?
银猫进食
The silver cat feeds--
当蓝在西边遇到黄
when blue meets yellow in the west--
去中国听上去不错  只要你轻轻走
A trip to China sounds nice-- If you tread lightly--
这周很长
The week is long--
银猫进食
The silver cat feeds--
真美
Beautiful,
是吧
isn't it?
凯伦
Hey, Karen.
你不介意我喊你凯伦吧
You don't mind if I call you Karen, do you?
很好
Good.
不
Oh, no.
不  破玩意
No. Piece of shit.
该死
Shit.
Damn it!
该死
Ah, shit.
Damn it!
破玩意
Piece of shit!
搞什么
What the hell?
是谁啊
Who's there?
我问  谁啊
I said, who's there?